A Guide to the Thomas Burr House Family Collection, 1890-1960
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
Thomas Burr House Family Collection, 1890-1960
The Edgar Cayce Foundation, Virginia Beach, Virginia
Coll.4
0.5 Linear Feet
House, Thomas Burr, Sr.; House, Carrie Salter; House, Thomas Burr, Jr.; House, Thomas Burr, III; House, Doris Anderson
Scope and Contents
The collection includes correspondence, ephemera, and photographs from the Thomas House Family of Hopkinsville, Kentucky. Thomas B. House Sr. married Gertrude Cayce's aunt, Carrie Salter. Carrie was the youngest sister of Gertrude's uncle, Hiram P. Salter. The collection contains materials belonging to Thomas House, Sr., Carrie Salter House, Thomas B. House, Jr., his wife Doris Anderson House, and their son Thomas House III.
Arrangement
1 box, arranged alphabetically.
- Box 1
  - book [The Biography of Our Baby], Thomas B. House Jr., 1908; Folder 1:1
  - correspondence [Thomas B. House Family], 1896-1949; Folder 1:2
  - correspondence, [Thomas B. House III], 1949; Folder 1:3
  - ephemera [Thomas B. House, Sr.], 1928-1929; Folder 1:4
  - photographs [Caroline Salter House], 1890-1949; Folder 1:5
  - photographs [Doris Anderson House], 1920-1980; Folder 1:6
  - photographs [Thomas B. House, Sr.], 1890-1929; Folder 1:7-1:8
  - photographs [Thomas B. House, Jr.], 1908-1960; Folder 1:9
  - photographs [Thomas B. House III], 1950-1965; Folder 1:10
  - photographs [Thomas B. House Sr. Family], 1909-1910; Folder 1:11
  - photographs [Thomas B. House Jr. Family], 1930-1960; Folder 1:12
  - scrapbook cover [Washington and Lee University], undated; Folder 1:13